scylladb.com 2019-12-02

# Privacy Policy - ScyllaDB

**ScyllaDB Ltd.**  
 **Privacy Notice**  
Recently Updated: August 2018

ScyllaDB Ltd. and its subsidiaries (collectively, “ **ScyllaDB** ” or “ **Us** ”) are committed to your right to privacy.

This Privacy Notice (“ **Privacy Notice** ”) governs the processing and transfer of Personal Data collected in connection with our websites, available at: [www.ScyllaDB.com](https://www.scylladb.com/), [cloud.scylladb.com](https://cloud.scylladb.com/), [university.scylladb.com](https://university.scylladb.com/) ,[www.osv.io](http://www.osv.io/), [www.cloudius-systems.com](http://www.cloudius-systems.com/) and [www.seastar.io](http://www.seastar.io/) (collectively, “ **Websites** ”) to each person (“ **User** ” or “ **You** ”) accessing or using the Websites and or services provided on the Website or otherwise provided by us (“ **Services** ”).

If you choose to interact with the Websites, register or use the Services, or otherwise provide data to us, you explicitly agree to the use of such data in accordance with this Privacy Notice. You may not use the Websites or Services or submit any data through them if you do not agree to any of the terms hereunder. This Privacy Notice shall not be construed in any manner to derogate from our Terms of Use or any other agreement or understanding between ScyllaDB and you.

**THE HIGHLIGHTS:**

  * You are not required by law to provide us with any Personal Data. Sharing Personal Data with us is entirely voluntary.

  * If you choose to provide us with data about you, you explicitly agree to the use of your data as specified in this Notice.

  * Our Services are intended for Users over the age of 16 or equivalent minimum age for providing consent to processing of Personal Data in the relevant jurisdiction. Children under such age are not permitted to use the Services. If you are under such age you should cease to use the Services immediately.

  * You may be entitled under applicable law to request to review, amend, erase or restrict the processing of your Personal Data. Please note that in case you request to erase or restrict the processing of your Personal Data, your use of the Services may be restricted or disabled.

  * We do not sell, trade, or rent Users’ Personal Data to third parties. We only share Personal Data with third parties in connection with the provision of the Services to our Users, or other limited circumstances as specified herein.

  * If you have any questions or requests regarding the processing of your Personal Data, or would otherwise like to contact us in connection with this Privacy Notice, please send us an email to: [privacy@scylladb.com](mailto:privacy@scylladb.com).

1.1 Personal Data

 **“Personal Data”** means any information which identifies or can be used to identify a natural person, including, but not limited to, first and last name, phone number, email address, IP address, billing information, etc.

1.1.1. When you interact with our Websites or Services, we may collect certain information about you, such as email, name, phone number and other contact information, session duration, page impressions, advertisements viewed or clicked on, and Internet protocol (IP) address.

1.1.2. The Scylla software reports certain information to us by default, including but not limited to the version of Scylla installed on a node. By installing Scylla software in its default configuration you agree to such collection of data.

1.1.3. You may at any time disable data collection by reconfiguring our products and the Services accordingly, but please be aware that it may prevent us from providing some or all of the Services to you.

1.2. Non-Personal Data

1.2.1. We collect non-Personal Data regarding Users concerning their use of the Websites and Services, such the browser and/or device type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request, etc.

1.2.2. We also may use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Websites. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.

2.1 Non-Personal Data  

Non-Personal Data is used mainly for click stream analysis in order to constantly improve and maintain our Websites and Services, including among others, in order to measure and understand the level of engagement to our Services, for general business analytics and in order to provide a more personalized experience and tailored content, for ensuring the technical functioning of our network, to help prevent fraudulent use of our Services and for developing new services and features.

2.2. Personal Data

Personal Data it is used only for the following purposes:

2.2.1. To provide our Users and clients with the Services.

2.2.2. To prevent potentially prohibited or illegal activities, fraud, misappropriation, infringements, identity thefts and any other misuse of the Websites or the Services.

2.2.3. To protect the security or integrity of our databases and the Services, and to take precautions against legal liability.

2.2.4. To improve the Services, and to develop new features, products and services.

2.2.5. For the purposes of our legitimate interests, to the extent not overridden by the rights and freedoms of natural persons, as permitted under applicable law.

3.1. Yes, we use data files such as cookies, pixel tags, “Flash cookies”, or other local storage files provided by your browser or associated applications ( **“Cookies”** ). We use these technologies in order to help ensure that your account security is not compromised; mitigate risk and prevent fraud; and to promote trust and safety across our sites and Services.

3.2. Cookies can be placed on your device by the websites or Services operator such as ScyllaDB, when you visit our websites or use our Services, such Cookies constitute – “ **first party”** Cookies, or by a party other than ScyllaDB, in which case the Cookies will constitute – **“third party”** Cookies.

3.3. Cookies can be differentiated by their time of use:

3.3.1. **“Session Cookies”** are Cookies that exists between the time you visit a websites and the time you ended the particular browsing session. Session Cookies expire and are automatically deleted when you close your internet browser.

3.3.2. **“Persistent Cookies”** are Cookies that stay on your device – they do not expire and are not automatically deleted when you close your browser. The length of time Persistent Cookies stay on your device varies from Cookie to Cookie.

3.4. We use third-party tracking services that employ cookies and page tags to collect data about visitors to our websites. This data includes usage and user statistics. Additionally, emails sent by ScyllaDB include page tags that collect information about who opened those emails and clicked on links in them.

3.5. You may at any time program your browser to block cookies, but please be aware that such blocking may prevent us from providing some or all of the Services to you. These cookies help us track how visitors use the Websites and our Services.

3.6. If you wish not to receive Cookies from us, with the exception of technical Cookies, you may notify us by following the instructions for opting out of such Cookies on our websites and applications or sending us an email to: [privacy@scylladb.com](mailto:privacy@scylladb.com). If you are accessing our websites from the EEA, we will not use third-party Cookies and persistent Cookies unless such use is permitted under the laws applicable to you.

3.7. If you have any questions about how we use Cookies not answered in this statement, you may contact us by sending us an email to: [privacy@scylladb.com](mailto:privacy@scylladb.com).

4.1. **Reviewing and amending your Personal Data.** You may send us a request in connection with reviewing your Personal Data to: [privacy@scylladb.com](mailto:privacy@scylladb.com). In the event any Personal Data is incorrect or outdated, you may update and correct such data by providing us with appropriate notification or correcting the data directly on the Websites, if applicable to you.

4.2. **Right of erasure and restriction**. You may also be entitled to request the erasure or the restriction of your Personal Data, and we will comply with such requests, to the extent required under applicable law.

4.3. **Portability of Personal Data.** To the extent relevant to you and to the Services, you may be entitled to request the portability of your Personal Data, and we will comply with such requests, to the extent required under applicable law.

4.4. **Retention of** **Data.** We reserve the right to retain any Personal Data for as long as reasonably necessary in order to: (i) fulfill the purposes described herein; (ii) in the defense or assertion of legal claims and liability; (iii) for the analysis and development of the Services; and (iv) to comply with applicable law. Non-Personal Data and statistical anonymized data may be retained by us without limitation.

5.1. WE DO NOT SELL OR RENT ANY OF YOUR PERSONAL DATA TO NON-AFFILIATED THIRD PARTIES FOR THEIR MARKETING PURPOSES **.**

5.2. Non-Personal Data, aggregate and statistical or otherwise anonymized data may be shared without limitation with third parties at our discretion. This information does not contain Personal Data and is used to develop content and services for our Users and clients.

5.3. We share certain data with our customers for their business purposes; however such data is anonymized prior to disclosure with the customer, and cannot identify any specific person.

5.4. We share Personal Data only under the following limited circumstances:

5.4.1. With trusted partners and third parties who assist us in operating the Services and conducting our business, such as fraud prevention and technology services.

5.4.2. As necessary to help detect and prevent potentially illegal acts and fraud, and to guide decisions about products, services and communications.

5.4.3. With our affiliates and connected companies, such as subsidiaries, sister-companies and parent companies.

5.4.4. To comply with a legal requirement, for the administration of justice, to protect your vital interests or the vital interests of others, to protect the security or integrity of our databases or the Services, to take precautions against legal liability, or in the event of a corporate sale, merger, reorganization, dissolution or similar event.

5.4.5. Other third parties with your consent or direction to do so.

5.5. We engage and collaborate with the following third-party service providers and data processors in connection with our Websites and Services. We may share data regarding your use of our Services with these providers. We encourage you to review the privacy notices of the third parties specified below, by following the appropriate links.

Drift: <https://www.drift.com/privacy-policy/>

Recurly: <https://recurly.com/legal/>

Stripe: <https://stripe.com/us/privacy>

Facebook: <https://www.facebook.com/privacy>

GitHub: <https://help.github.com/articles/github-privacy-statement/>

Marketo: <https://documents.marketo.com/legal/privacy/>

MailChimp: <https://mailchimp.com/legal/privacy/>

Twitter: <https://twitter.com/en/privacy>

LinkedIn: <https://www.linkedin.com/legal/privacy-policy>

Just Media: <http://justmedia.com/privacy-policy/>

OneTrust: <https://www.onetrust.com/privacy-policy/>

Google Tag Manager: <https://policies.google.com/privacyhttps://privacy.google.com/businesses/processorterms/>

Google Adwords: <https://policies.google.com/privacy>

Google Analytics: ScyllaDB uses the “User ID” feature of Google Analytics. The amount of information that you share with Google depends on your privacy settings.

6.1. Certain processing activities conducted by us are based on the necessity of such activities for the performance of our Services and the contract between us and our visitors and business partners.

6.2. Other processing activities are based on the grounds that they are necessary for the purposes of our legitimate interests or the legitimate interests of a third party, except where such interests are overridden by the interests or fundamental rights and freedoms of natural persons which require protection of Personal Data.

6.3. There may be certain processing activities based on your consent. In connection with such activities, you may rescind your consent, by sending us an email to: [privacy@scylladb.com](mailto:privacy@scylladb.com) Please note that in the event you rescind your consent to the processing of Personal Data, we may not be able to provide you with some or all of the Services.

ScyllaDB is a global enterprise, with offices in various territories around the world. If you are accessing our Services from a territory other than that in which we process data, data may be transferred across international borders. In addition, Some of ScyllaDB employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country. By accessing and using our Services you explicitly agree to such international transfers.

From time to time, we send Users promotion information via direct mailing such as emails. We will not send any User within regions protected by GDPR such promotional mailing without obtaining those Users’ explicit prior consent.

Our Websites are general audience Websites, which are not directed to persons under 16 years old. If a parent or guardian becomes aware that his/her child has provided us with Personal Data without their consent, he/she should contact us immediately. We do not knowingly collect or solicit Personal Data from people under 16 years old. If we become aware that a person under 16 years old has provided us with Personal Data, we will delete such data from our databases.

The provisions included in this Notice relating to matters regulated under the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) will apply only to the processing of Personal Data which is subject to the GDPR in accordance with the applicability provisions contained therein. If the GDPR does not apply to the processing of your Personal Data, some of the provisions above may not apply to you.

If you have any questions or concerns regarding privacy issues, please send us a detailed message to [privacy@scylladb.com](mailto:privacy@scylladb.com) and we will make every effort to resolve your concerns without delay.

ScyllaDB may, at any time and from time to time, modify this Privacy Notice. Modifications to this Privacy Notice will be posted on the Websites, and shall be effective as of the date in which they are posted on the Websites.

You may also be entitled to file a complaint with the appropriate supervisory authority in connection with concerns you may have with regards to your privacy and Personal Data.
